<resources>
    <string name="app_name">E Blogger</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="new_app_name">E-Blogger</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="admob_id_label">Enter your AdMob Banner Ad Unit Id</string>
    <string name="admob_id_hint">Google AdMob Banner Ad Unit Id</string>
    <string name="test_ad_id">For eg. ca-app-pub-3940256099942544/6300978111</string>
    <string name="submit_button">Submit</string>
    <string name="dialog_fire_missiles">Fire it Man</string>
    <string name="fire">fire</string>
    <string name="cancel">cancel</string>
    <string name="app_motto">Earn more by writing well</string>

    <string name="terms_conditions_0">
        By creating a E-Blogger account, whether through a mobile device, mobile application or computer (collectively, the “Service”)
        you agree to be bound by these Terms of Use (this “Agreement”).
        If you wish to create a E-Blogger account and make use of the Service, please read this Agreement.
    </string>


    <string name="terms_conditions_1">The content used in blogs must be real and original.
        \n\nNo copy pasted content will be allowed in blogs.\n\nIf any blog is found to be copy pasted,
        then that particular blog will be deleted and warning will be issued to the user.</string>

    <string name="terms_conditions_2">No use of unacceptable, disgraceful, intolerable and bad words will be allowed in the content.
        \n\nBlogs having use of such language will be deleted.</string>

    <string name="terms_conditions_3">No vulgar content and images will be allowed in the blogs.
        \n\nIf any blog with vulgar, pornographic content is found then that particular user\'s account will be blocked.</string>

    <string name="terms_conditions_4">Content of blog must be readable to all age groups.
        \n\nContent of blog should not be based on any false information or hatred towards any religion, caste and creed.
        \n\nContent based on fake news and falsified information should be strictly prohibited and
        appropriate action will be taken against the user.</string>

    <string name="terms_conditions_5">Do not use multiple Google AdMob accounts to get the clicks and impressions on your own blogs.
        Otherwise your AdMob account will be blocked by Google and we can not help you in that case.
        Still you will be able to use E-Blogger application, create and access all of your blogs.</string>

    <string name="terms_conditions_6">Adding more Terms and Conditions soon...</string>

    <string name="faq_1">
        <b> 1. How I can earn with E-Bogger App? </b>
        \n&#160;- You need to monetize your Blogs in order to earn through Blogs. More the Blogs, more the earning!
    </string>

    <string name="faq_2">
        <b> 2. What does it mean to monetize the Blogs? </b>
        \n&#160;- Whenever you create a Blog in E-Blogger Application, we will load your Google AdMob Ad on your Blog.
        You can not see your own Ad on your own Blog. Other people will be able to see your Ads on your Blogs.
    </string>

    <string name="faq_3">
        <b> 3. Why I can not see my own Ad on my own Blogs? </b>
        \n&#160;- To prevent from invalid clicks and impressions we do not allow users to see their own Ads on their own Blogs.
        Even the Google AdMob\'s policy has this rule. Google AdMob will block your account if you click on your own Ads and make earnings.

    </string>

    <string name="faq_4">
        <b> 4. What is required to monetize a Blog? </b>
        \n&#160;- All you need is a Google AdMob account with a Banner Ad Unit Id. You need to enter your Banner Ad Unit Id on
        Monetization section of E-Blogger App and we will handle the rest.
    </string>

    <string name="faq_5">
        <b> 5. How to get Google AdMob Banner Ad Unit Id? </b>
        \n&#160;&#160;- a. Go to \"https://apps.admob.com\" and create AdMob account.
        \n&#160;&#160;b. Once you create a AdMob account, you will be redirected to Google AdMob console. Open the left panel and click on \"Apps\".
        \n&#160;&#160;c. Click on \"Add Your First App\" button. You will be asked, \"Have you published your Application on Google Play or the App Store?\" - Click \"No\".
        \n&#160;&#160;d. Give any name to your Application and select platform as \"Android\". Click \"Add\" button.
        \n&#160;&#160;e. You will get your AdMob App Id. Now click on \"Create Ad Unit\" button.
        \n&#160;&#160;f. Select \"Banner\" as a ad format in the next step.
        \n&#160;&#160;g. Give any name to your Ad Unit. Do not change any advanced settings.
        \n&#160;&#160;h. Once you give name to your Ad Unit, click on \"Create Ad Unit\" button.
        \n&#160;&#160;i. You are done! You will see your Banner Ad Unit Id. Remember Banner Ad Unit Id is the one which contains \"/\" in between.
        \n&#160;&#160;<b>Note: If you see \"Missing Payment Information\" on your Google AdMob homepage then you should add payment info. Google will just ask you for your address
        in order to receive further communications. If you failed to do this step then you won\'t receive Ads for your Banner Ad Unit Id. </b>
    </string>

    <string name="faq_6">
        <b> 6. What to do once I have Banner Ad Unit Id? </b>
        \n&#160;- As we said above, Just copy your AdMob banner Ad Unit Id and paste it on Monetization section of E-Blogger App and click Submit. We will remember your Banner Ad Unit Id
        whenever you create a new Blog and we will load your Ad on your Blogs.
    </string>

    <string name="faq_7">
        <b> 7. What happens when I submit my Banner Ad Unit Id on E-Blogger App? </b>
        \n&#160;- Banner Ad Unit Id is like a container where we will give some space of our application to load Ads in your Banner Ad. That space will be on your Blog, so it is
        a great tool to monetize and earn throug your Blogs.
    </string>

    <string name="faq_8">
        <b> 8. Is Monetizing a Blog is mandatory to use this E-Blogger App? </b>
        \n&#160;- No. It is not mandatory to monetize your Blogs. You can simply create Blogs as much as you want without having any AdMob account.
    </string>

    <string name="faq_9">
        <b> 9. Can I enter more than one Banner Ad Unit Id on Monetization Screen? </b>
        \n&#160;- No. It is recommended that you should have only one Banner Ad Unit Id associated with one E-Blogger account.
    </string>

    <string name="faq_10">
        <b> 10. Where should I reach if I have doubts/questions? </b>
        \n&#160;- You can reach us at <b> info@eonline.org.in </b>.
    </string>

    <string-array name="blog_categories">
        <item>Travelling</item>
        <item>Food</item>
        <item>Technology</item>
        <item>Politics</item>
        <item>Socialism</item>
        <item>Gym</item>
        <item>Fitness and Nutrition</item>
        <item>Gaming</item>
        <item>Bollywood and entertainment</item>
        <item>Apparels</item>
        <item>Cosmetics</item>
        <item>Health</item>
        <item>Personal Care and Hygiene</item>
        <item>Business</item>
        <item>Science</item>
        <item>Studies</item>
        <item>History</item>
        <item>Programming</item>
        <item>Cars and Bikes</item>
        <item>Advertisement and Promotion</item>
        <item>others</item>
    </string-array>






    <!-- OAuth 2.0 Web Application type client Id -->
    <string name="client_id">208525305220-hq4b7qa997di3qlbj3ol7dp8teo058jq.apps.googleusercontent.com</string>
</resources>
